Guide to the Harriet Wasserman Literary Agency Records, 1940s-2000 and undated (bulk 1978-1995) RL.00509
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, A-Z, 1941-1995
  - Writings (Open) Subseries, A-Z, 1948-1995 and undated
    - McPhee, Charles
      - Stop Sleeping Through Your Dreams: A Guide to Awakening Consciousness During Dream Sleep, undated (Box WO-18)
    - Meir, Menahem
      - My Mother, Golda Meir, undated, 3 folders (Box WO-18)
    - Mooney, Ted
      - Traffic and Laughter, 1984-1991, 4 versions in 5 folders (Box WO-18)
    - Mooney, Ted (continued) (Box WO-19)
      - Traffic and Laughter (continued), 1984-1991, 1 version in 3 folders (Box WO-19)
    - Myers, Walter Dean
      - A Black Experience in Children's Books: One Step Forward, Two teps Back (print), undated (Box WO-19)
      - The Black Pearl and the Ghost, undated (Box WO-19)
      - Death of a Champion (print), undated (Box WO-19)
    - Nunez, Sigrid
      - A Feather on the Breath of God, 1994 and undated), 2 versions in 3 folders (Box WO-19)
      - Italies (print), 1992 Winter (Box WO-19)
    - Price, Reynolds
      - Annunciation (print, inscribed) 1975 Christmas (Box WO-19)
      - August Snow, 1989-1990, 3 folders; folders 2 and 3 are print (Box WO-19)
      - Better Days, 1989 July (Box WO-19)
      - Blue Calhoun, undated, 1 version in 3 folders (Box WO-19)
      - Broad Day (print), 1975 Winter (Box WO-19)
      - A Child's Christmas in North Carolina (Box WO-19)
      - Clear Pictures, 1988 April 11, 1 version in 2 folders (Box WO-19)
      - Commencing (print), 1975 Spring (Box WO-19)
      - A Day in the Life of a Porch (print), 1992 June (Box WO-19)
      - Deeds of Light (print), 1992-1993 Winter (Box WO-19)
      - The Enormous Door (print), 1991 Spring (Box WO-19)
      - Family Stories: The Carters in Plains (print), 1977 January 3 (Box WO-19)
      - The Foreseeable Future, undated, 1 version in 2 folders; dedicated (Box WO-19)
      - The Fourth Eclogue of Vergil (print), 1972 Christmas (Box WO-19)
      - Full Day (print), 1991 January (Box WO-19)
      - Full Day and Interview (with Susan Ketchin; print), 1991 January (Box WO-19)
      - A Generous Man (print), 1969 (Box WO-19)
      - Good Hearts, 1986 October (Box WO-19)
      - A Gourmet Childhood (print), 1993 (Box WO-19)
      - His Final Mother (print), 1990 May 21 (Box WO-19)
      - In a Dim Warm Cave (print), 1984 January (Box WO-19)
      - Kate Vaiden (Box WO-19)
        see Starting a Life in Box WO-20
      - Letter to a Young Writer (print), 1985 (Box WO-19)
      - The Lost Room (print), 1992 June 11 (Box WO-19)
      - Love Across the Lines, 1983 and undated, 2 folders; folder 2 is print (Box WO-19)
      - Michael Egerton (print), 1985 (Box WO-19)
      - New Music, 1989 (Box WO-19)
      - A New Stretch Of Woods, 1989, 2 printings (Box WO-19)
      - Night and Day at Panacea, 1974 March 26 (Box WO-19)
      - Night Dance, 1989 July 7 (Box WO-19)
      - The Promise of Rest, 1990 September 30, 1 folder (Box WO-19)
    - Price, Reynolds (continued) (Box WO-20)
      - The Promise of Rest (continued), 1990 September 30 and 1995, 2 versions in 3 folders (Box WO-20)
      - Self-Portrait (drawing), 1975 January 11 (Box WO-20)
      - Serious Need, 1990 November and 1992, 2 printings in 2 folders (Box WO-20)
      - Starting a Life (print excerpt from Kate Vaiden), 1986 Spring/Summer (Box WO-20)
      - The Strangest Story, 1990 (Box WO-20)
      - The Tongues of Angels, 1987 October 1 (Box WO-20)
      - Toward Home, 1990 and 1992, 2 folders; folder 2 is print (Box WO-20)
      - Two Useful Visits (print), 1990 Summer (Box WO-20)
      - Vision of Healing (print), 1994 August (Box WO-20)
      - Walking Lessons, undated (Box WO-20)
      - A Whole New Life, undated, 1 version in 2 folders (Box WO-20)
      - A Sign of Blood, undated (Box WO-20)
    - Schwartz, Adele Aron
      - Once, undated (Box WO-20)
    - Seldes, Lee
      - The Legacy of Mark Rothko, 1985 April (Box WO-20)
    - Seuling, Barbara
      - A Day At Coney Island (print), 1976 July (Box WO-20)
    - Sheraton, Mimi
      - Is Salami and Eggs Better than Sex? Memoirs of a Happy Eater, undated (Box WO-20)
      - My Favorite New York Restaurants (print), 1978 October 10 (Box WO-20)
    - Sourian, Peter
      - Introduction to The Forty Days of Musa Dagh 1990 October 23 (Box WO-20)
    - Tax, Meredith
      - The Bright Future (i.e. Union Square), 1985 and undated, 5 versions in 7 folders (Box WO-20)
      - Opinion (print), undated (Box WO-20)
      - The Sound of One Hand Capping (print), 1988 Fall (Box WO-20)
      - Time To Save Children's Lives (print), 1988 April 11 (Box WO-20)
      - Union Square: A Proposal (i.e. The Bright Future), undated (Box WO-20)
      - A Woman and Her Mind (print), 1970 (Box WO-20)
    - Travers, P.L
      - On Not Writing for Children, undated (Box WO-20)
      - The Rose and the Egg, undated (Box WO-20)
      - Well, Shoot Me! undated (Box WO-20)
    - Walter, Eugene
      - Delectable Dishes from Termite Hall, undated (Box WO-20)
      - Undine (translation of German original by Friedrich Heinrich Karl La Motte-Fouqué), undated (Box WO-20)
    - Wilcox, James
      - Modern Baptists, 1981 December 7 (Box WO-20)
    - Williams, Jay
      - The Christmas Thief (print), 1975 December (Box WO-20)
      - Danny Dunn and the Universal Glue, undated (Box WO-20)
      - Duke Pishposh of Pash (print), 1978 February (Box WO-20)
      - The Practical Princess (print), undated (Box WO-20)
      - The Question Box (print), 1980 January (Box WO-20)
      - The Reward Worth Having (print), 1977 July (Box WO-20)
    - Williams, Victoria
      - The Water of Life, undated (Box WO-20)
    - Winegardner, Mark
      - The Veracruz Blues, 1995 and undated), 2 versions in 3 folders (Box WO-20)
    - Witty, Helen
      - Fancy Pantry, 1985 (Box WO-20)
  - Writings (Books) Subseries, A-Z, 1944-1994 and undated
    This subseries consists of authors' published book length works. Included are first American editions and paperbacks, translations, special or limited editions, uncorrected bound proofs, and some seventy books with acknowledgements, dedications, and/or inscriptions to Harriet Wasserman (N.B.: see under Wasserman's name in the Miscellaneous (Open) Subseries for photocopies of these pages). A count and brief summary of editions is given after each title. The absence of this summary indicates that there is a single copy of an American hardback edition with no acknowledgement, dedication, or inscription. The entire subseries of about 840 items is open. For unbound proofs or published versions with authors' handwritten corrections, see the Writings (Open) Subseries.
    - Amoss, Berthe, 18 (Box WB-1)
      - The Big Cry (Box WB-1)
      - By the Sea (Box WB-1)
      - The Chalk Cross (Box WB-1)
      - Delicious Dishes: Creole Cooking for Children
        - paperback: American (Box WB-1)
      - Old Hasdrubal and the Pirates (Box WB-1)
      - The Loup Garou (Box WB-1)
      - The Marvelous Catch of Old Hannibal (Box WB-1)
      - The Mockingbird Song (Box WB-1)
      - The Mysterious Prowler, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-1)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-1)
      - Old Hannibal and the Hurricane (Box WB-1)
      - Secret Lives, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-1)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-1)
      - Tom in the Middle (Box WB-1)
      - The Very Worst Thing (Box WB-1)
      - The Witch Cat
        - paperback: American (Box WB-1)
      - What Did You Lose, Santa? (Box WB-1)
      - Louisiana Women Writers: New Essays and a Comprehensive Bibliography (inscribed by Amoss, with an essay about her) (Box WB-1)
    - Arnold, Emily, 2
      - A Craving
        - paperback: American (Box WB-1)
      - Life Drawing
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-1)
    - Bach, Richard, 2
      - Running from Safety, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-1)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-1)
    - Bausch, Richard, 19
      - The Fireman's Wife and Other Stories, 2
        - paperback: American (Box WB-1)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-1)
      - The Last Good Time, 2
        - hardback: German (Box WB-1)
        - paperback: American/unittitle> (Box WB-1)
      - Mr. Field's Daughter, 2
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-1)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-1)
      - Rare and Endangered Species: A Novella and Stories, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-1)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-1)
      - Real Presence, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-1)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-1)
      - Rebel Powers, 2
        - hardback: American (acknowledged and inscribed) (Box WB-1)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-1)
      - Spirits and Other Stories, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-1)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-1)
      - Take Me Back (Box WB-1)
      - Violence, 4
        - hardback: American (inscribed, with poem "Poem for Harriet" inscribed on front end papers); Spanish (Argentina) (Box WB-1)
        - uncorrected bound proof, 2, with one inscribed (Box WB-1)
    - Bellow, Saul, 232 (Box WB-2)
      - The Adventures Of Augie March, 11
        - hardback: Czech, English (British, Indian), Hungarian (2), Japanese (Box WB-2)
        - paperback: British, Dutch (2 printings), Spanish, French (2 volumes) (Box WB-2)
      - The Bellarosa Connection, 21
        - hardback: American (inscribed), Danish, Finnish, German, Italian (2 printings), Japanese, Norwegian, Swedish (Box WB-2)
        - paperback: American (one fair copy and one with proofreader's corrections), Spanish (2), Dutch, French, Hungarian, Portuguese (Brazil), Spanish (Argentina), Spanish (Mexico), Italian (Box WB-2)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-2)
      - Dangling Man, 9
        - hardback: American, British, Polish (Box WB-2)
        - paperback: American (2 publishers), English (published in Japan) French, Italian, Portuguese (Box WB-2)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WB-3)
      - The Dean's December (30)
        - hardback: American (trade, limited, and slip cased editions), British, Dutch, Finnish, Hebrew, Italian, Japanese, Romanian, Serbo-Croatian, Swedish (2 publishers) (Box WB-3)
        - paperback: American (2 printings), Danish, Dutch, Finnish, French (2 publishers), Greek, Italian, Korean, Portuguese (Brazil), Romanian, Spanish (2 printings), Swedish (Box WB-3)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-3)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WB-4)
      - A Father-to-be and Looking For Mr. Green
        - paperback: English (published in Japan) (Box WB-4)
      - The Gonzaga Manuscripts
        - paperback: French (Box WB-4)
      - Henderson The Rain King, 11
        - hardback: British, Polish, Swedish, Portuguese, Czech (Box WB-4)
        - paperback: French, Italian (3 printings), Norwegian, Swedish (Box WB-4)
      - Herzog, 14
        - hardback: Spanish (Box WB-4)
        - paperback: Dutch, German, Hebrew, Italian (3 printings), Japanese (2 printings), Norwegian, Romanian, Serbo-Croatian, Spanish (Spain, 2 printings) (Box WB-4)
      - Herzog and Humboldt's Gift
        - hardback: Italian (Box WB-4)
      - Him With His Foot in His Mouth, 17
        - hardback: American, British, Finnish, Hebrew, Italian (2 publishers), Norwegian, Polish, Swedish (Box WB-4)
        - paperback: American, Belgian, Danish, French (2 editions), Spanish (Spain) (Box WB-4)
        - uncorrected bound proof (2 versions) (Box WB-4)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WB-5)
      - Him With His Foot In His Mouth (continued) (Box WB-5)
      - Humboldt's Gift, 14
        - hardback: French (2 vols), German, Italian, Japanese, Slovenian (Box WB-5)
        - paperback: American (trade edition and special edition), Czech, Polish, Portuguese, Spanish (2 publishers) (Box WB-5)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-5)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WB-6)
      - It All Adds Up, 7
        - hardback: American (acknowledged), Italian (acknowledged) (Box WB-6)
        - paperback: American, French, Portuguese (Brazil) (Box WB-6)
        - uncorrected bound proofs, 2 versions (Box WB-6)
      - Looking For Mr. Green and Other Stories, 2
        - hardback: Czech, 2 publishers (Box WB-6)
      - Mr. Sammler's Planet, 10
        - hardback: American (Box WB-6)
        - paperback: American British; Danish, Hebrew, Italian (2 pubs), Japanese; Portuguese; Swedish (Box WB-6)
      - More Die of Heartbreak, 20
        - hardback: British, Italian (2 printings) (Box WB-6)
        - paperback: British (2 printings), Italian, British large print; Danish; Dutch; English pub. in Korea; Finnish; French; Hebrew; Korean; Norwegian; Portuguese; Serbo-Croatian, Spanish (2) (Box WB-6)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-6)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WB-7)
      - More Die of Heartbreak (continued) (Box WB-7)
      - Mosby's Memoirs, 4
        - paperback: Japanese, Danish, Dutch, French (Box WB-7)
      - Orange Soufflé, in Traverse Plays
        - paperback: British (Box WB-7)
      - Salmagundi: Saul Bellow--Literature and Culture
        - paperback: special issue on Saul Bellow (Box WB-7)
      - Seize the Day, 11
        - hardback American (4 editions), English (published in Germany), Swedish (Box WB-7)
        - paperback: American, Portuguese, Basque, Spanish; Hungarian (Box WB-7)
      - Short Stories
        - paperback: English (published in Japan) (Box WB-7)
      - A Silver Dish
        - paperback: Dutch (Box WB-7)
      - Something to Remember Me By, 6
        - hardback: American (traded and signed/numbered edition), Italian (check on signed ed--pbk. or hbk?) (Box WB-7)
        - paperback: American, Dutch, French (Box WB-7)
      - A Theft, 22
        - hardback: American, British, Italian (2 publishers), Japanese, Norwegian (Box WB-7)
        - paperback: Danish, Dutch, French, German, Greek, Hebrew, Italian, Korean, Portuguese (Brazil), Spanish (Argentina, Mexico (2 publishers), Spain), Swedish advance reading copies (one uncorrected and one with proofreader's corrections) (Box WB-7)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WB-8)
      - To Jerusalem and Back, 6
        - hardback: American (Box WB-8)
        - paperback: American, Spanish (two publishers) (Box WB-8)
        - uncorrected bound proof, two versions (Box WB-8)
      - The Victim, 9
        - hardback: British, Finnish, Italian (Box WB-8)
        - paperback: American, British, German, Italian, Spanish, Swedish (Box WB-8)
    - Biddle, Wayne, 4
      - Barons of the Sky, 2
        - paperback: American (Box WB-8)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-8)
      - A Field Guide to Germs, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-8)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-8)
    - Birnbaum, Phyllis
      - An Eastern Tradition (Box WB-8)
    - Bloom, Allan, 16
      - The Closing of the American Mind (9)
        - paperback: Danish, English (excerpt printed in Japan), Hebrew, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Norwegian (excerpt), Portuguese (Brazil), Spanish (Box WB-8)
        - paperback: Polish (Box WB-25)
      - Giants and Dwarfs (4) (Box WB-8)
        - hardback: American (Box WB-8)
        - paperback: Portuguese (Brazil) Spanish (Argentina) (Box WB-8)
        - advance uncorrected reader's proof (Box WB-8)
      - Love and Friendship (2)
        - hardback: American (Box WB-8)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-8)
    - Brown, Wesley, 2 (Box WB-9)
      - Boogie Woogie and Booker T
        - paperback: American (Box WB-9)
      - Tragic Magic (Box WB-9)
    - Bolton, Ruthie, 4
      - Gal: A True Life
        - hardback: American (Box WB-9)
        - paperback: American, 3 editions (Box WB-9)
    - Bonner, John Tyler, 3
      - Cells and Societies
        - paperback: American (Box WB-9)
      - Life Cycles: Reflections of an Evolutionary Biologist
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-9)
      - The Scale of Nature
        - paperback: American (Box WB-9)
    - Buechner, Frederick, 20
      - The Alphabet of Grace (Box WB-9)
      - The Book of Bebb (Box WB-9)
      - The Clown in the Belfrey, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-9)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-9)
      - The Final Beast, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-9)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-9)
      - Godric
        - paperback: Dutch (Box WB-9)
      - Listening to Your Life
        - paperback: American (Box WB-9)
      - The Magnificent Defeat
        - paperback: American (Box WB-9)
      - Now and Then (Box WB-9)
      - Peculiar Treasures
        - paperback: German (Box WB-9)
      - A Room Called Remember (Box WB-9)
      - The Sacred Journey
        - paperback: Dutch (Box WB-9)
      - The Son of Laughter (Box WB-9)
      - Telling Secrets (Box WB-9)
      - Telling the Truth: The Gospel as Tragedy, Comedy, and Fairy Tale (Box WB-9)
      - Whistling in the Dark: An ABC Theologized (Box WB-9)
      - Wishful Thinking: A Theological ABC, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-9)
        - paperback: French (Box WB-9)
      - The Wizard's Tide (Box WB-9)
    - Cable, Mary, 7
      - Avery's Knot
        - hardback: American (Box WB-9)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-9)
      - The Blizzard of '88
        - hardback: American (Box WB-9)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-9)
      - The Little Darling: A History of Child Rearing in America (Box WB-9)
      - Tell Me About Love
        - hardback: American (dedicated) (Box WB-9)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-9)
      - Top Drawer: American High Society from the Gilded Age to the Roaring Twenties
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-9)
    - Cameron, Sara, 3
      - Natural Enemies
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-9)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-9)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-9)
    - Clark, Eleanor, 9 (Box WB-10)
      - The Bitter Box (Box WB-10)
      - Camping Out (Box WB-10)
      - The Oysters of Locmariaquer, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-10)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-10)
      - Rome and a Villa, 4
        - hardback: American, 2 publishers (Box WB-10)
        - paperback: American, 2 publishers (Box WB-10)
      - Tamrat: 13 Days in the Sahara
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-10)
    - Cohen, Charles, 2
      - Daddy (Box WB-10)
      - Falling Out (Box WB-10)
    - Coolidge, Olivia
      - The Apprenticeship of Abraham Lincoln (Box WB-10)
    - Davis, Lydia, 2
      - Break it Down (Box WB-10)
      - Sketches for a Life of Wassilly
        - paperback: American (Box WB-10)
    - DeHaven, Tom, 5
      - Freaks' Amour, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-10)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-10)
      - Funny Papers
        - paperback: American (Box WB-10)
      - Sunburn Lake, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-10)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-10)
    - Delving, Michael--see Jay Williams (Box WB-10)
    - Dorian, Marguerite, 3
      - The Quality of Witness (Box WB-10)
      - The Seasons (Box WB-10)
      - The Year of the Waterbearer (Box WB-10)
    - Engelson, Joyce
      - Mountain of Villainy: a Triplicity (Box WB-10)
    - Fairchild, William, 2
      - No Man's Land
        - hardback: American (Box WB-10)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-10)
    - Fields, Maxine
      - Baby Names From Around the World
        - paperback: American (Box WB-10)
    - Flanagan, Dennis
      - Flanagan's Version: A Spectator's Guide to Science on the Eve of the 21st Century
        - hardback: American (acknowledged), English (India) (Box WB-10)
        - paperback: Arabic (Jordan), English, French (Box WB-10)
        - uncorrected bound proof (acknowledged) (Box WB-10)
    - Gee, Maggie, 2 (Box WB-11)
      - The Burning Book (Box WB-11)
      - Light Years (Box WB-11)
    - Gertler, T.
      - Elbowing the Seducer (Box WB-11)
    - Glickfeld, Carole L.
      - Useful Gifts
        - hardback: American (inscribed) (Box WB-11)
    - Goldstein, Rebecca, 11
      - The Dark Sister, 3
        - hardback: American (Box WB-11)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-11)
      - The Late-Summer Passion of a Woman of Mind, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-11)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-11)
      - Mazel, 2
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-11)
        - paperback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-11)
      - The Mind-Body Problem, 2 (Box WB-11)
      - Strange Attractors, 3
        - hardback: American (Box WB-11)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-11)
      - Greenwald, Sheila, 29 (Box WB-11)
      - All the Way to Wits' End, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-11)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
      - Alvin Webster's Surefire Plan for Success (and How It Failed), 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-11)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
      - The Atrocious Two, 2
        - hardback: American (dedicated), Swedish (Box WB-11)
      - Bad Friends Good Friends
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
      - Blissful Joy and the SATs (Box WB-11)
      - Give us a Great Big Smile, Rosy Cole, 2
        - hardback (Japanese) (Box WB-11)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
      - The Hot Day (Box WB-11)
      - The Mariah Delany Lending Library Disaster
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
      - Mariah Delany's Author-of-the-Month Club (Box WB-11)
      - Mat Pit and the Tunnel Tenants (Box WB-11)
      - A Metropolitan Love Story (Box WB-11)
      - Miss Amanda Snap (Box WB-11)
      - My Fabulous New Life
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
      - Rosy Cole Discovers America! (Box WB-11)
      - Rosy Cole's Great American Guilt Club, 2
        - hardback: American, 2 printings (Box WB-11)
      - Rosy's Romance
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
      - The Secret in Miranda's Wardrobe, 2
        - paperback: American, 2 printings (Box WB-11)
      - The Seventh Cousin (Box WB-11)
      - Willie Bryant and the Flying Otis (Box WB-11)
      - Will the Real Gertrude Hollings Please Stand Up?, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-11)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
      - Write On, Rosy! (A Young Author in Crisis), 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-11)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-11)
    - Hassler, Jon, 15 (Box WB-12)
      - Four Miles to Pinecone, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-12)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-12)
      - Grand Opening (Box WB-12)
      - A Green Journey, 3
        - hardback: American, British (Box WB-12)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-12)
      - Jemmy (Box WB-12)
      - The Love Hunter, 4
        - hardback: Finnish (2 publishers), Norwegian (Box WB-12)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-12)
        - uncorrected bound proof (Box WB-12)
      - Simon's Night, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-12)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-12)
      - Staggerford, 2
        - hardback: American (Box WB-12)
        - paperback: American (Box WB-12)
    - Heller, Erica, 2
      - Splinters
        - hardback: American (acknowledged) (Box WB-12)
        - uncorrected bound proof (acknowledged) (Box WB-12)
    - Hijuelos, Oscar (35)
      - Introduction to Cool Salsa (Box WB-12)
      - The Fourteen Sisters of Emilio Montez O'Brien, 7
        - hardback: American, Finnish (Box WB-12)
        - paperback: Korean, Dutch, English, Spanish (Box WB-12)
    - Hijuelos, Oscar (continued) (Box WB-13)
      - The Mambo Kings Play Songs of Love, 22
        - hardback: Italian, Japanese (2 volumes), Swedish, Norwegian (Box WB-13)